<gameList>
<game id="4221" source="ScreenScraper">
	<path>./Ace Combat Advance (USA, Europe).gba</path>
	<name>Ace Combat Advance</name>
	<desc>The Air Strike Force (A.S.F.) is the most advanced aircraft squadron on the planet. Not held by any nation, they are owned by General Resources Ltd. who begins to assign the A.S.F. to duties designed to destroy competition and put them at an economic advantage. Alarmed by this dominance, the nations of the world ally themselves to form the United Air Defense (U.A.D.) whose goal is to fight the war on the A.S.F. and destroy their weapons capability.

Ace Combat Advance is a top-down shooter. The player begins by picking an aircraft and secondary weapon type to use on each mission. Upon entering the level, the player is able to rotate left, right and perform a dive maneuver, while at the same time thrust and breaking can be applied. For weapons the player is able to fire a cannon directly in front of the plane or fire the secondary weapon, the specifics of which vary. A briefing showing each of the  12 mission''s objectives and defined targets.</desc>
	<image>~/.emulationstation/downloaded_images/gba/Ace Combat Advance (USA, Europe)-mix-no-video.png</image>
	<rating>0.6</rating>
	<releasedate>00000000T000000</releasedate>
	<developer>Atari</developer>
	<publisher>Namco</publisher>
	<genre>Shooter</genre>
	<players>1</players>
</game>
<game id="3782" source="ScreenScraper">
	<path>./Advance Wars (USA).gba</path>
	<name>Advance Wars</name>
	<desc>This turn-based strategy game hails back to a classic Japanese strategy game titled Famicom Wars. Advance Wars pits players against very computer AI in a number of battles involving submarines, warships, infantry, tanks, helicopters, and other weapons. During the maps, players may capture buildings to increase financial resources and repair damaged units. During combat, two units go head to head with the results determined by how the two stack up against each other, terrain conditions, and other factors. Up to four players can play using the Game Link Cable or by swapping a single Game Boy Advance at the end of each player's turn.</desc>
	<image>~/.emulationstation/downloaded_images/gba/Advance Wars (USA)-mix-no-video.png</image>
	<rating>0.8</rating>
	<releasedate>00000000T000000</releasedate>
	<developer>Intelligent Games</developer>
	<publisher>Nintendo</publisher>
	<genre>Strategy</genre>
	<players>1-4</players>
</game>
<game id="4441" source="ScreenScraper">
	<path>./Aero the Acro-Bat - Rascal Rival Revenge (USA).gba</path>
	<name>Aero the Acro-Bat</name>
	<desc>You play as bat Aero, who have to stop the mad scientist Edgar Ektor, who is trying to rid the world of amusement and fun. So you jump through the circus-style levels, using different kinds of machines such as catapults, cannons, bubble machines, platforms, etc., collecting various power-ups such as cheese, soda, keys, clocks, etc. and avoiding lethal obstacles.</desc>
	<image>~/.emulationstation/downloaded_images/gba/Aero the Acro-Bat - Rascal Rival Revenge (USA)-mix-no-video.png</image>
	<rating>1</rating>
	<releasedate>00000000T000000</releasedate>
	<developer>Metro3D</developer>
	<publisher>Atomic Planet</publisher>
	<genre>Action</genre>
	<players>1</players>
</game>
<game id="4262" source="ScreenScraper">
	<path>./Aggressive Inline (USA).gba</path>
	<name>Aggressive Inline</name>
	<desc>In Aggressive Inline the player takes the role of one of nine real-life skaters with one specific goal: receiving as much points as possible by performing spectacular stunts. Every of the 13 courses also has various special challenges, e.g. collecting or smashing certain items, which need to be performed to beat it. In contrast to the open areas of the console versions this one features more linear levels and tight time limits. 

It also replaces the "juice meter" with the so-called "grind meter" which is filled up by performing stunts. Every grind decreases this meter and if it is empty no grinds can be performed at all. Of course grinds are an elemental move to beat the challenges. 
There is also a freestyle playing mode where the player can unlock new skaters.
The soundtrack is licensed.</desc>
	<image>~/.emulationstation/downloaded_images/gba/Aggressive Inline (USA)-mix-no-video.png</image>
	<rating>0.65</rating>
	<releasedate>00000000T000000</releasedate>
	<developer>Full Fat</developer>
	<publisher>Acclaim Entertainment</publisher>
	<genre>Shooter</genre>
	<players>1-2</players>
</game>
<game id="3933" source="ScreenScraper">
	<path>./Aladdin (USA) (En,Fr,De,Es).gba</path>
	<name>Aladdin</name>
	<desc>Game Boy Advance adaptation of the classic Super NES platformer version from Capcom. Closely based on the Disney hit animated movie Aladdin, this side-scrolling platformer lets you take the role of Aladdin and his mischievous pal monkey, Abu. Using anything they can find, this prince of thieves and his sidekick throw apples, and ride magic carpets to get their chance with destiny. The game introduced many now familiar platform game elements to gamers, such as ziplines and multi-character gameplay. The Game Boy Advance version of the game isn't a simple Super NES port; each stage has new original gameplay not found in the game released on the SNES.</desc>
	<image>~/.emulationstation/downloaded_images/gba/Aladdin (USA) (En,Fr,De,Es)-mix-no-video.png</image>
	<rating>0.75</rating>
	<releasedate>00000000T000000</releasedate>
	<developer>Capcom</developer>
	<publisher>Capcom</publisher>
	<genre>Puzzle-Game</genre>
	<players>1</players>
</game>
<game id="4297" source="ScreenScraper">
	<path>./Alex Rider - Stormbreaker (USA).gba</path>
	<name>Alex Rider : Stormbreaker</name>
	<desc>Embrace the role of Alex Rider to out-spy, outwit and out-cool evil. Based on the teen spy movie, Alex Rider: Stormbreaker starring Mickey Rourke, Alicia Silverstone and Ewan McGregor, the video game captures all the excitement and suspense of Anthony Horowitz's best-selling novel about teenage superspy Alex Rider. Game play includes combat, stealth missions, vehicles and the use of gadgets to achieve mission objectives. Explore Ian Rider's house, the breaker's yard, MI6's secret Liverpool Street headquarters, M16's training facilities and Darius Sayle's complex. Players obtain mission briefings from Mrs. Jones and Alan Blunt before they go undercover, improve their problem-solving skills at M16's top training camp and receive spy gadgets from Smithers to aid them in combat, navigation and unlocking special mini games.</desc>
	<image>~/.emulationstation/downloaded_images/gba/Alex Rider - Stormbreaker (USA)-mix-no-video.png</image>
	<rating>0.85</rating>
	<releasedate>00000000T000000</releasedate>
	<developer>Razorback Developments</developer>
	<publisher>THQ</publisher>
	<genre>Action</genre>
	<players>1</players>
</game>
<game id="4149" source="ScreenScraper">
	<path>./Alien Hominid (Europe) (En,Fr,De,Es,It).gba</path>
	<name>Alien Hominid</name>
	<desc>You're a little yellow alien.  The FBI has shot down your ship while flying over planet Earth.  And it, quite literally, lands right on their doorstep.  After a series of FBI Agents swipe your ship, what option do you have other than to blow up everything in your path to get it back?

Alien Hominid is a 2D side-scrolling shooter with heavy references to the Metal Slug series of games - from the hand-drawn graphics, huge explosions, right down to the ability to eviscerate FBI Agents when you get up close to them.  The graphics are by featured artist Dan Paladin.  Your goal, is quite simply, to get to the end of the stage, and die as little as possible.  Which is made difficult due to the fact that any bullet is an instant kill.

To help you out, you can grab a range of power-ups, such as lasers, spread shots, shotguns and more, as well as hijacking vehicles and using them for protection.  Grenades can be lobbed, and you can jump on enemy shoulders and choose to bite their heads off if you like, or pick them up and throw them at other enemies.  You can also dive underground for a short period of time to avoid enemies - while underground, you can drag agents into the ground to kill them.

The GBA version of the game is identical in gameplay, however, with a few bosses removed (such as the robot bee and the FBI big-fisted tank robot).  The PlayStation 2, Xbox and Xbox 360 versions of the game include a special "PDA Game" with very simple-looking graphics.  Your goal in this game is to kill all the agents by hopping on their heads, and then reach the exit.  Included with this game is a level editor, allowing you to make your own levels and then send them to friends if you have the Xbox or Xbox 360 version.</desc>
	<image>~/.emulationstation/downloaded_images/gba/Alien Hominid (Europe) (En,Fr,De,Es,It)-mix-no-video.png</image>
	<rating>0.5</rating>
	<releasedate>00000000T000000</releasedate>
	<developer>Zoo Digital</developer>
	<publisher>Zoo Digital</publisher>
	<genre>Shooter</genre>
	<players>1</players>
</game>
<game id="4139" source="ScreenScraper">
	<path>./Altered Beast - Guardian of the Realms (USA).gba</path>
	<name>Altered Beast : Guardian of the Realms</name>
	<desc/>
	<image>~/.emulationstation/downloaded_images/gba/Altered Beast - Guardian of the Realms (USA)-mix-no-video.png</image>
	<rating>0.6</rating>
	<releasedate>20021125T000000</releasedate>
	<developer>THQ</developer>
	<publisher>Sega</publisher>
	<genre>Action</genre>
	<players/>
</game>
<game id="4372" source="ScreenScraper">
	<path>./American Dragon - Jake Long - Rise of the Huntsclan (USA, Europe) (En,Fr,De,Es,It).gba</path>
	<name>American Dragon : Jake Long</name>
	<desc/>
	<image>~/.emulationstation/downloaded_images/gba/American Dragon - Jake Long - Rise of the Huntsclan (USA, Europe) (En,Fr,De,Es,It)-mix-no-video.png</image>
	<rating>0.5</rating>
	<releasedate>00000000T000000</releasedate>
	<developer>Buena Vista Interactive</developer>
	<publisher>Wayforward Technologies</publisher>
	<genre>Platform</genre>
	<players>1</players>
</game>
<game id="4383" source="ScreenScraper">
	<path>./American Tail, An - Fievel's Gold Rush (USA) (En,Es).gba</path>
	<name>An American Tail: Fievel's Gold Rush</name>
	<desc>Fievel Mousekewitz, a rodent with an immigration card, is heading west in An American Tail: Fievel's Gold Rush. Based on the animated series from Universal Studios, the game has players controlling Fievel as he travels through 18 levels and six worlds, including "New York City" and "Gold Dust Gulch," to piece together Cat Malone's treasure map. Fievel will swing on rope, attack with his ten-gallon hat, ride riverboats, and jump the train to find Wylie Burp's gold.</desc>
	<image>~/.emulationstation/downloaded_images/gba/American Tail, An - Fievel's Gold Rush (USA) (En,Es)-mix-no-video.png</image>
	<rating>0.75</rating>
	<releasedate>00000000T000000</releasedate>
	<developer>Hokus Pokus</developer>
	<publisher>Swing! Entertainement</publisher>
	<genre>Platform</genre>
	<players>1</players>
</game>
<game id="4426" source="ScreenScraper">
	<path>./Ant Bully, The (USA) (En,Fr).gba</path>
	<name>The Ant Bully</name>
	<desc/>
	<image>~/.emulationstation/downloaded_images/gba/Ant Bully, The (USA) (En,Fr)-mix-no-video.png</image>
	<rating>0</rating>
	<releasedate>00000000T000000</releasedate>
	<developer>Midway</developer>
	<publisher>A2M</publisher>
	<genre>Adventure</genre>
	<players>1</players>
</game>
<game id="4361" source="ScreenScraper">
	<path>./Antz - Extreme Racing (USA).gba</path>
	<name>Fourmiz Extreme Racing</name>
	<desc/>
	<image>~/.emulationstation/downloaded_images/gba/Antz - Extreme Racing (USA)-mix-no-video.png</image>
	<rating>0.85</rating>
	<releasedate>00000000T000000</releasedate>
	<developer>Empire Interactive</developer>
	<publisher>Empire Interactive</publisher>
	<genre>Race, Driving</genre>
	<players>1-2</players>
</game>
<game id="4308" source="ScreenScraper">
	<path>./Army Men - Operation Green (USA) (En,Fr,De,Es,It).gba</path>
	<name>Army Men : Operation Green</name>
	<desc/>
	<image>~/.emulationstation/downloaded_images/gba/Army Men - Operation Green (USA) (En,Fr,De,Es,It)-mix-no-video.png</image>
	<rating>0.85</rating>
	<releasedate>00000000T000000</releasedate>
	<developer>Panasonic</developer>
	<publisher>Panasonic</publisher>
	<genre>Educational</genre>
	<players>1</players>
</game>
<game id="4547" source="ScreenScraper">
	<path>./ATV - Quad Power Racing (USA, Europe).gba</path>
	<name>ATV Quad Power Racing</name>
	<desc/>
	<image>~/.emulationstation/downloaded_images/gba/ATV - Quad Power Racing (USA, Europe)-mix-no-video.png</image>
	<rating>0</rating>
	<releasedate>00000000T000000</releasedate>
	<developer>Acclaim Entertainment</developer>
	<publisher>Acclaim Entertainment</publisher>
	<genre>Race, Driving</genre>
	<players/>
</game>
<game id="3861" source="ScreenScraper">
	<path>./Avatar - The Last Airbender (USA).gba</path>
	<name>Avatar: The Last Airbender</name>
	<desc>Water. Earth. Fire. Air.rnrnAre you ready to face your destiny?rnrnJourney through 6 exotic locations filled with adventure to help Aang fulfill his destiny to master the bending arts and become the Avatar - for only the Avatar can stop the ruthless might of the Fire Nation! Defeat hordes of bizarre enemies and perform noble deeds on your quest to save the world.</desc>
	<image>~/.emulationstation/downloaded_images/gba/Avatar - The Last Airbender (USA)-mix-no-video.png</image>
	<rating>0.6</rating>
	<releasedate>00000000T000000</releasedate>
	<developer>Studio Oz</developer>
	<publisher>THQ</publisher>
	<genre>Adventure</genre>
	<players>1</players>
</game>
<game id="3733" source="ScreenScraper">
	<path>./Backyard Baseball (USA).gba</path>
	<name>Backyard Baseball</name>
	<desc>Create the baseball team of your dreams! It's great baseball action with the backyard kids and real pro players as kids. Pick your team, choose logos and playing fields. Play single games, an entire season or Home Run Derby. It's the chance of a lifetime to play with the pros right in your own backyard. Play single Games or a whole season, choose from all 30 Major League Baseball teams, create, save and trade custom players, practice your swing in the Home Run Derby, and track player and team stats in Season play. Also features a two-player multiplayer mode when linking up two Game Boy Advance units via a link cable.</desc>
	<image>~/.emulationstation/downloaded_images/gba/Backyard Baseball (USA)-mix-no-video.png</image>
	<rating>0</rating>
	<releasedate>20020000T000000</releasedate>
	<developer>Humongous Entertainment</developer>
	<publisher>Atari</publisher>
	<genre>Sports</genre>
	<players/>
</game>
<game id="3914" source="ScreenScraper">
	<path>./Banjo-Kazooie - Grunty's Revenge (USA, Europe).gba</path>
	<name>Banjo-Kazooie: Grunty's Revenge</name>
	<desc/>
	<image>~/.emulationstation/downloaded_images/gba/Banjo-Kazooie - Grunty's Revenge (USA, Europe)-mix-no-video.png</image>
	<rating>0.8</rating>
	<releasedate>00000000T000000</releasedate>
	<developer>Rareware</developer>
	<publisher>THQ</publisher>
	<genre>Platform</genre>
	<players>1</players>
</game>
<game id="3999" source="ScreenScraper">
	<path>./Batman - Vengeance (USA) (En,Fr,Es).gba</path>
	<name>Batman Vengeance</name>
	<desc/>
	<image>~/.emulationstation/downloaded_images/gba/Batman - Vengeance (USA) (En,Fr,Es)-mix-no-video.png</image>
	<rating>0.7</rating>
	<releasedate>00000000T000000</releasedate>
	<developer>Ubisoft</developer>
	<publisher>Ubisoft</publisher>
	<genre/>
	<players>1</players>
</game>
<game id="4070" source="ScreenScraper">
	<path>./Batman Begins (USA, Europe) (En,Fr,De,Es,It,Nl).gba</path>
	<name>Batman Begins</name>
	<desc>Follow the story of the movie through a multitude of highly interactive levels spanning various locations. Control Bruce Wayne as he trains in the Himalayas, caught off-guard as he narrowly escapes an attack on his mansion, and as Batman using a variety of acrobatic moves and combo-driven attacks. Fight off challenging AI and use gadgets from the Bat Belt against bosses including Ra's Al Ghul and The Scarecrow. The game presents a rich graphical environment full of interactive and environmental objects utilizing real-time lighting and alpha effects.</desc>
	<image>~/.emulationstation/downloaded_images/gba/Batman Begins (USA, Europe) (En,Fr,De,Es,It,Nl)-mix-no-video.png</image>
	<rating>0.6</rating>
	<releasedate>00000000T000000</releasedate>
	<developer>Electronic Arts</developer>
	<publisher>Electronic Arts</publisher>
	<genre>Action</genre>
	<players>1</players>
</game>
<game id="78334" source="ScreenScraper">
	<path>./BattleBots - Design &amp; Destroy (USA).gba</path>
	<name>BattleBots - Design &amp; Destroy</name>
	<desc/>
	<image>~/.emulationstation/downloaded_images/gba/BattleBots - Design &amp; Destroy (USA)-mix-no-video.png</image>
	<rating>0</rating>
	<releasedate>00000000T000000</releasedate>
	<developer/>
	<publisher/>
	<genre>Action</genre>
	<players/>
</game>
</gameList>